{
    "subject": "resource/Recordland",
    "predicate": "property/products",
    "object": "Compact Discs, DVDs",
    "human_readable": "Recordland produces Compact Discs and DVDs.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9192326068878174,
            "question": "Does Recordland manufacture Compact Discs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7820444107055664,
            "question": "Is DVD production a part of Recordland's business?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6542624831199646,
            "question": "What does Recordland manufacture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5952824950218201,
            "question": "Does Recordland produce music or video media?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5071298480033875,
            "question": "What types of media does Recordland produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49564749002456665,
            "question": "What is Recordland known for making?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3935900926589966,
            "question": "Recordland specializes in what kind of entertainment products?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3558800518512726,
            "question": "What products are associated with the company Recordland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29720595479011536,
            "question": "Give an example of a product made by Recordland."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29052042961120605,
            "question": "Name two types of media made by Recordland."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Recordland produces Compact Discs and DVDs.",
            "html": "dbpedia_369_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Give an example of a product made by Recordland.",
            "html": "dbpedia_369_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What products are associated with the company Recordland?",
            "html": "dbpedia_369_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Recordland specializes in what kind of entertainment products?",
            "html": "dbpedia_369_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_369_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_369_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_369_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_369_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_369_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_369_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_369_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_369_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_369_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_369_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents provided focus on Recordland as a store specializing in vinyl records. There's no mention of them producing CDs or DVDs.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the requested format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents does not mention Recordland producing Compact Discs or DVDs. The texts only discuss Recordland as a store that specializes in selling used and new records, CDs (in the context of people trying them before buying), but there is no indication that they produce these items themselves."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do not contain any information supporting that Recordland produces Compact Discs or DVDs. Recordland is described as a music store specializing in various genres of vinyl records, with no mention of producing CDs or DVDs."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Recordland specializes in vinyl records, not compact discs or DVDs.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "All provided text focuses on Recordland as a store specializing in vinyl records and its massive collection. There is no mention of Recordland producing Compact Discs or DVDs.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Recordland Limited is a music store specializing in vinyl records and various genres of music, with no indication that they produce compact discs or DVDs.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Recordland Limited specializes in music records (vinyl) and does not produce or sell Compact Discs (CDs) or DVDs.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}